This app works best with JavaScript enabled.

* Sinch Email
    
    Sinch Email

* About
    
    About

* [Blog
    
    Blog](https://www.mailgun.com/blog/)
    
* Help
    
    Help

* [Documentation
    
    Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    
* [Log in
    
    Log in](https://login.mailgun.com/login/)

* English
    
    English

* [Pricing
    
    Pricing](https://www.mailgun.com/pricing/)
* Products
    
    * [Send icon
        
        SendSend, receive, and track emails at any scale.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [API icon
            
            Send API](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-api/)
        * [Server icon
            
            SMTP](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/smtp/)
        * [Calendar icon
            
            Email Logs](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/logs/)
        * [Line chart up trend icon
            
            Email Analytics](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Routing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * [Bar line chart icon
        
        OptimizeImprove inbox placement and connect with more people.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Badge with checkmark icon
            
            Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-verification/)
        * [Crown icon
            
            Inbox Placement Testing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/inbox-placement/)
        * [Eye icon
            
            Email Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-testing-tool/preview-your-html-emails/)
        * [Warning sign icon
            
            Reputation Monitoring](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability/blocklist-monitoring-service/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Deliverability Services](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability-services/)
    * [Shield badge check icon
        
        ValidateClean your lists to improve your reputation.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Clock icon
            
            Real Time Validations](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-validation-api/)
        * [Checklist icon
            
            List Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation/)
        * [Checklist with check icon
            
            List Validation Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation-preview/)
        * [Click icon
            
            Engagement Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/engagement-validation/)
    
    Products
    
    * [Send icon
        
        SendSend, receive, and track emails at any scale.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [API icon
            
            Send API](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-api/)
        * [Server icon
            
            SMTP](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/smtp/)
        * [Calendar icon
            
            Email Logs](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/logs/)
        * [Line chart up trend icon
            
            Email Analytics](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Routing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * [Bar line chart icon
        
        OptimizeImprove inbox placement and connect with more people.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Badge with checkmark icon
            
            Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-verification/)
        * [Crown icon
            
            Inbox Placement Testing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/inbox-placement/)
        * [Eye icon
            
            Email Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-testing-tool/preview-your-html-emails/)
        * [Warning sign icon
            
            Reputation Monitoring](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability/blocklist-monitoring-service/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Deliverability Services](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability-services/)
    * [Shield badge check icon
        
        ValidateClean your lists to improve your reputation.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Clock icon
            
            Real Time Validations](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-validation-api/)
        * [Checklist icon
            
            List Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation/)
        * [Checklist with check icon
            
            List Validation Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation-preview/)
        * [Click icon
            
            Engagement Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/engagement-validation/)
    
* Industries
    
    * Retail icon
        
        CompaniesScale with an adaptable communications platform.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Suitcase icon
            
            Enterprise](https://www.mailgun.com/enterprise/)
        * [Handshake icon
            
            Partner](https://www.mailgun.com/about/partners/)
    * Office icon
        
        VerticalsSolutions based on your email workflows and business case.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chip icon
            
            Marketing Technologies](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/marketing-technology/)
        * [Laptop with money badge icon
            
            Fintech](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/fintech/)
        * [Medication icon
            
            Healthcare](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/healthcare/)
    
    Industries
    
    * Retail icon
        
        CompaniesScale with an adaptable communications platform.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Suitcase icon
            
            Enterprise](https://www.mailgun.com/enterprise/)
        * [Handshake icon
            
            Partner](https://www.mailgun.com/about/partners/)
    * Office icon
        
        VerticalsSolutions based on your email workflows and business case.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chip icon
            
            Marketing Technologies](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/marketing-technology/)
        * [Laptop with money badge icon
            
            Fintech](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/fintech/)
        * [Medication icon
            
            Healthcare](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/healthcare/)
    
* Solutions
    
    * Email icon
        
        Use CasesUnderstand how Mailgun fits into your email needs.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Open email icon
            
            Transactional Emails](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/transactional-email/)
        * [Discount icon
            
            Email Marketing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-marketing/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Parsing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-parsing/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Email Receiving](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * Trophy icon
        
        Success StoriesMeasurable results from real customers.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chess piece icon
            
            Mailgun vs. Competitors](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/comparisons/esp-comparisons/)
        * [Document icon
            
            Case studies](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/)
    
    Solutions
    
    * Email icon
        
        Use CasesUnderstand how Mailgun fits into your email needs.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Open email icon
            
            Transactional Emails](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/transactional-email/)
        * [Discount icon
            
            Email Marketing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-marketing/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Parsing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-parsing/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Email Receiving](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * Trophy icon
        
        Success StoriesMeasurable results from real customers.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chess piece icon
            
            Mailgun vs. Competitors](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/comparisons/esp-comparisons/)
        * [Document icon
            
            Case studies](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/)
    
* Developer
    
    * [Badge question icon
        
        Help Center](https://help.mailgun.com/hc/en-us)
    * [Layers icon
        
        SDKs](https://documentation.mailgun.com/docs/mailgun/sdk/introduction/)
    * [Code icon
        
        Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    * [Headset icon
        
        Contact Support](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/support/)
    * [Plugs icon
        
        Integrations](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/integrations/)
    
    Developer
    
    * [Badge question icon
        
        Help Center](https://help.mailgun.com/hc/en-us)
    * [Layers icon
        
        SDKs](https://documentation.mailgun.com/docs/mailgun/sdk/introduction/)
    * [Code icon
        
        Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    * [Headset icon
        
        Contact Support](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/support/)
    * [Plugs icon
        
        Integrations](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/integrations/)
    
* Resources
    
    * [Lightbulb icon
        
        LearnExplore our resources packed with expert email advice.](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Book icon
            
            Guides](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/guides/)
        * [Magnifying glass icon
            
            Research reports](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/)
        * [Microphone icon
            
            Podcasts](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/podcasts/)
        * [Video icon
            
            Videos](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/videos/)
        * [Book with bookmark icon
            
            Glossary](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/learn/glossary/)
        * [Layout icon
            
            Email Templates](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/tools/email-templates/)
    * [
        
        Building a dynamic email ecosystem: SparkToro's story
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/sparktoro/)
    * [
        
        State of email deliverability 2025
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/state-of-email-deliverability/)
    
    Resources
    
    * [Lightbulb icon
        
        LearnExplore our resources packed with expert email advice.](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Book icon
            
            Guides](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/guides/)
        * [Magnifying glass icon
            
            Research reports](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/)
        * [Microphone icon
            
            Podcasts](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/podcasts/)
        * [Video icon
            
            Videos](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/videos/)
        * [Book with bookmark icon
            
            Glossary](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/learn/glossary/)
        * [Layout icon
            
            Email Templates](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/tools/email-templates/)
    * [
        
        Building a dynamic email ecosystem: SparkToro's story
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/sparktoro/)
    * [
        
        State of email deliverability 2025
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/state-of-email-deliverability/)
    
* Contact
    
    * [Handshake icon
        
        Contact Sales](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/sales/)
    * [Calendar icon
        
        Schedule a demo](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/schedule-a-demo/)
    
    Contact
    
    * [Handshake icon
        
        Contact Sales](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/sales/)
    * [Calendar icon
        
        Schedule a demo](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/schedule-a-demo/)

Back to main menu

* [Pricing
    
    Pricing](https://www.mailgun.com/pricing/)
* Products
    
    * [Send icon
        
        SendSend, receive, and track emails at any scale.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [API icon
            
            Send API](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-api/)
        * [Server icon
            
            SMTP](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/smtp/)
        * [Calendar icon
            
            Email Logs](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/logs/)
        * [Line chart up trend icon
            
            Email Analytics](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Routing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * [Bar line chart icon
        
        OptimizeImprove inbox placement and connect with more people.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Badge with checkmark icon
            
            Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-verification/)
        * [Crown icon
            
            Inbox Placement Testing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/inbox-placement/)
        * [Eye icon
            
            Email Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-testing-tool/preview-your-html-emails/)
        * [Warning sign icon
            
            Reputation Monitoring](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability/blocklist-monitoring-service/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Deliverability Services](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability-services/)
    * [Shield badge check icon
        
        ValidateClean your lists to improve your reputation.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Clock icon
            
            Real Time Validations](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-validation-api/)
        * [Checklist icon
            
            List Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation/)
        * [Checklist with check icon
            
            List Validation Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation-preview/)
        * [Click icon
            
            Engagement Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/engagement-validation/)
    
    Products
    
    * [Send icon
        
        SendSend, receive, and track emails at any scale.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [API icon
            
            Send API](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-api/)
        * [Server icon
            
            SMTP](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/smtp/)
        * [Calendar icon
            
            Email Logs](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/logs/)
        * [Line chart up trend icon
            
            Email Analytics](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Routing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * [Bar line chart icon
        
        OptimizeImprove inbox placement and connect with more people.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Badge with checkmark icon
            
            Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-verification/)
        * [Crown icon
            
            Inbox Placement Testing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/inbox-placement/)
        * [Eye icon
            
            Email Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-testing-tool/preview-your-html-emails/)
        * [Warning sign icon
            
            Reputation Monitoring](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability/blocklist-monitoring-service/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Deliverability Services](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability-services/)
    * [Shield badge check icon
        
        ValidateClean your lists to improve your reputation.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Clock icon
            
            Real Time Validations](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-validation-api/)
        * [Checklist icon
            
            List Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation/)
        * [Checklist with check icon
            
            List Validation Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation-preview/)
        * [Click icon
            
            Engagement Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/engagement-validation/)
    
* Industries
    
    * Retail icon
        
        CompaniesScale with an adaptable communications platform.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Suitcase icon
            
            Enterprise](https://www.mailgun.com/enterprise/)
        * [Handshake icon
            
            Partner](https://www.mailgun.com/about/partners/)
    * Office icon
        
        VerticalsSolutions based on your email workflows and business case.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chip icon
            
            Marketing Technologies](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/marketing-technology/)
        * [Laptop with money badge icon
            
            Fintech](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/fintech/)
        * [Medication icon
            
            Healthcare](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/healthcare/)
    
    Industries
    
    * Retail icon
        
        CompaniesScale with an adaptable communications platform.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Suitcase icon
            
            Enterprise](https://www.mailgun.com/enterprise/)
        * [Handshake icon
            
            Partner](https://www.mailgun.com/about/partners/)
    * Office icon
        
        VerticalsSolutions based on your email workflows and business case.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chip icon
            
            Marketing Technologies](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/marketing-technology/)
        * [Laptop with money badge icon
            
            Fintech](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/fintech/)
        * [Medication icon
            
            Healthcare](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/healthcare/)
    
* Solutions
    
    * Email icon
        
        Use CasesUnderstand how Mailgun fits into your email needs.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Open email icon
            
            Transactional Emails](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/transactional-email/)
        * [Discount icon
            
            Email Marketing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-marketing/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Parsing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-parsing/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Email Receiving](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * Trophy icon
        
        Success StoriesMeasurable results from real customers.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chess piece icon
            
            Mailgun vs. Competitors](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/comparisons/esp-comparisons/)
        * [Document icon
            
            Case studies](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/)
    
    Solutions
    
    * Email icon
        
        Use CasesUnderstand how Mailgun fits into your email needs.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Open email icon
            
            Transactional Emails](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/transactional-email/)
        * [Discount icon
            
            Email Marketing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-marketing/)
        * [Segmentation icon
            
            Email Parsing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-parsing/)
        * [Inbox icon
            
            Email Receiving](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
    * Trophy icon
        
        Success StoriesMeasurable results from real customers.
        
        * * *
        
        * [Chess piece icon
            
            Mailgun vs. Competitors](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/comparisons/esp-comparisons/)
        * [Document icon
            
            Case studies](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/)
    
* Developer
    
    * [Badge question icon
        
        Help Center](https://help.mailgun.com/hc/en-us)
    * [Layers icon
        
        SDKs](https://documentation.mailgun.com/docs/mailgun/sdk/introduction/)
    * [Code icon
        
        Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    * [Headset icon
        
        Contact Support](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/support/)
    * [Plugs icon
        
        Integrations](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/integrations/)
    
    Developer
    
    * [Badge question icon
        
        Help Center](https://help.mailgun.com/hc/en-us)
    * [Layers icon
        
        SDKs](https://documentation.mailgun.com/docs/mailgun/sdk/introduction/)
    * [Code icon
        
        Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    * [Headset icon
        
        Contact Support](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/support/)
    * [Plugs icon
        
        Integrations](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/integrations/)
    
* Resources
    
    * [Lightbulb icon
        
        LearnExplore our resources packed with expert email advice.](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Book icon
            
            Guides](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/guides/)
        * [Magnifying glass icon
            
            Research reports](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/)
        * [Microphone icon
            
            Podcasts](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/podcasts/)
        * [Video icon
            
            Videos](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/videos/)
        * [Book with bookmark icon
            
            Glossary](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/learn/glossary/)
        * [Layout icon
            
            Email Templates](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/tools/email-templates/)
    * [
        
        Building a dynamic email ecosystem: SparkToro's story
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/sparktoro/)
    * [
        
        State of email deliverability 2025
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/state-of-email-deliverability/)
    
    Resources
    
    * [Lightbulb icon
        
        LearnExplore our resources packed with expert email advice.](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/)
        
        * * *
        
        * [Book icon
            
            Guides](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/guides/)
        * [Magnifying glass icon
            
            Research reports](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/)
        * [Microphone icon
            
            Podcasts](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/podcasts/)
        * [Video icon
            
            Videos](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/videos/)
        * [Book with bookmark icon
            
            Glossary](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/learn/glossary/)
        * [Layout icon
            
            Email Templates](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/tools/email-templates/)
    * [
        
        Building a dynamic email ecosystem: SparkToro's story
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/sparktoro/)
    * [
        
        State of email deliverability 2025
        
        Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/state-of-email-deliverability/)
    
* Contact
    
    * [Handshake icon
        
        Contact Sales](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/sales/)
    * [Calendar icon
        
        Schedule a demo](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/schedule-a-demo/)
    
    Contact
    
    * [Handshake icon
        
        Contact Sales](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/sales/)
    * [Calendar icon
        
        Schedule a demo](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/schedule-a-demo/)

* Sinch Email
    
    Sinch Email

* About
    
    About

* [Blog
    
    Blog](https://www.mailgun.com/blog/)
    
* Help
    
    Help

* [Documentation
    
    Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
    
* [Log in
    
    Log in](https://login.mailgun.com/login/)

* English
    
    English

* [Send icon
    
    SendSend, receive, and track emails at any scale.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/)
    
    * * *
    
    * [API icon
        
        Send API](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-api/)
    * [Server icon
        
        SMTP](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/smtp/)
    * [Calendar icon
        
        Email Logs](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/logs/)
    * [Line chart up trend icon
        
        Email Analytics](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/email-analytics/)
    * [Segmentation icon
        
        Email Routing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
* [Bar line chart icon
    
    OptimizeImprove inbox placement and connect with more people.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/)
    
    * * *
    
    * [Badge with checkmark icon
        
        Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-verification/)
    * [Crown icon
        
        Inbox Placement Testing](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/inbox-placement/)
    * [Eye icon
        
        Email Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/email-testing-tool/preview-your-html-emails/)
    * [Warning sign icon
        
        Reputation Monitoring](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability/blocklist-monitoring-service/)
    * [Inbox icon
        
        Deliverability Services](https://www.mailgun.com/products/optimize/deliverability-services/)
* [Shield badge check icon
    
    ValidateClean your lists to improve your reputation.](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/)
    
    * * *
    
    * [Clock icon
        
        Real Time Validations](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-validation-api/)
    * [Checklist icon
        
        List Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation/)
    * [Checklist with check icon
        
        List Validation Preview](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/email-list-validation-preview/)
    * [Click icon
        
        Engagement Validation](https://www.mailgun.com/products/validate/engagement-validation/)

* Retail icon
    
    CompaniesScale with an adaptable communications platform.
    
    * * *
    
    * [Suitcase icon
        
        Enterprise](https://www.mailgun.com/enterprise/)
    * [Handshake icon
        
        Partner](https://www.mailgun.com/about/partners/)
* Office icon
    
    VerticalsSolutions based on your email workflows and business case.
    
    * * *
    
    * [Chip icon
        
        Marketing Technologies](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/marketing-technology/)
    * [Laptop with money badge icon
        
        Fintech](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/fintech/)
    * [Medication icon
        
        Healthcare](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/industries/healthcare/)

* Email icon
    
    Use CasesUnderstand how Mailgun fits into your email needs.
    
    * * *
    
    * [Open email icon
        
        Transactional Emails](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/transactional-email/)
    * [Discount icon
        
        Email Marketing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-marketing/)
    * [Segmentation icon
        
        Email Parsing](https://www.mailgun.com/solutions/use-cases/email-parsing/)
    * [Inbox icon
        
        Email Receiving](https://www.mailgun.com/products/send/inbound-routing/)
* Trophy icon
    
    Success StoriesMeasurable results from real customers.
    
    * * *
    
    * [Chess piece icon
        
        Mailgun vs. Competitors](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/comparisons/esp-comparisons/)
    * [Document icon
        
        Case studies](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/)

* [Badge question icon
    
    Help Center](https://help.mailgun.com/hc/en-us)
* [Layers icon
    
    SDKs](https://documentation.mailgun.com/docs/mailgun/sdk/introduction/)
* [Code icon
    
    Documentation](https://documentation.mailgun.com/)
* [Headset icon
    
    Contact Support](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/support/)
* [Plugs icon
    
    Integrations](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/integrations/)

* [Lightbulb icon
    
    LearnExplore our resources packed with expert email advice.](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/)
    
    * * *
    
    * [Book icon
        
        Guides](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/guides/)
    * [Magnifying glass icon
        
        Research reports](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/)
    * [Microphone icon
        
        Podcasts](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/podcasts/)
    * [Video icon
        
        Videos](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/videos/)
    * [Book with bookmark icon
        
        Glossary](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/learn/glossary/)
    * [Layout icon
        
        Email Templates](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/tools/email-templates/)
* [
    
    Building a dynamic email ecosystem: SparkToro's story
    
    Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/case-studies/sparktoro/)
* [
    
    State of email deliverability 2025
    
    Read More](https://www.mailgun.com/resources/research/state-of-email-deliverability/)

* [Handshake icon
    
    Contact Sales](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/sales/)
* [Calendar icon
    
    Schedule a demo](https://www.mailgun.com/contact/schedule-a-demo/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy and security is of the utmost importance to us. We describe in this policy how we collect and use information about you in your use of our services, including our platform and the website. If you are one of our customers, you should read this policy in conjunction with our [Terms of Service](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/terms/).

1\. Who are we?
---------------

We are Sinch Email, the Developer & Email business unit of Sinch. This business unit comprises of the brands Mailgun, Mailjet, Email on Acid and InboxReady. The processing explained in this policy may be carried out by Sinch Email or other data controllers in the Sinch Group.

When collecting information about our customers or visitors of our website, we are, under European Union (“EU") data protection laws, qualified as “data controller". This means that we are responsible for deciding how we hold and use personal data about you.

2\. How do we collect your data?
--------------------------------

We collect information about you when you fill in a sign up or contact form on our website or send us an email. We may also receive your personal data from third parties, when you express your interest for our services to them.

We collect information by automated means. When you visit our website, view one of our advertisements on a third party-owned website, or read our marketing newsletters, we automatically collect information about you via cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies. These are small files associated with information that your browser or our servers will save and return as part of your use of the website and the services for purposes such as saving your login session between visits, remembering your display preferences, tracking your use of the website, and for audience measurement purposes. For more information on our use of cookies, read [our cookies notice](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/cookie-policy/).

3\. What data do we collect?
----------------------------

Personal data. This is information that lets us know who you are. This includes the information you provide us when registering to use the platform (i.e. your name, company name, email address, postal address, other contact information you share with us, associated domain name and credit card information). Your login credentials are also personal data. This category also includes information tied to your identity that you provide us through other means, such as emails to our support team.

Non-personal data. This is information that doesn’t let us determine your identity. This generally comes from your use of the services after registering on our website. Non-personal data includes information that could personally identify you in its original form, but that we have modified (for instance, by aggregation) any personal data.

In addition, and in the context of using our services, namely creating and sending emails, we have access to the information contained in the subject and content of the emails that you send out, as well as the email contacts you send to via our services.

The data you submit should not include any sensitive personal data, such as Government identifiers (i.e. social security, driving licence, or taxpayer identification numbers), complete credit card or complete personal bank card numbers, medical records or particulars connected with applications for care or treatment associated with private individuals.

4\. How do we use your data?
----------------------------

If you are a visitor of our website, we use your personal and non-personal data to engage with you and support live chat conversations on the website.

When you are one of our customers, we use the information we collect about you to provide the services to you. As part of that purpose, we use your data:

1. Badge Check
    
    to create and maintain your platform account, and to control access to it;
    
2. Badge Check
    
    to provide our services and facilitate performance, including verifications relating to you and for email verifications;
    
3. Badge Check
    
    to provide you with real-time logs of your use of the platform;
    
4. Badge Check
    
    to respond to any requests you may submit for support or sales information, or similar communications;
    
5. Badge Check
    
    to communicate with you about our services (for example through newsletters, marketing emails, announcements or special offers);
    
6. Badge Check
    
    for billing and collection purposes, if you have subscribed to one of our paid plans;
    
7. Badge Check
    
    for the investigation, prevention and management of fraud and for breaches of our Terms of service;
    
8. Badge Check
    
    to enable third parties to provide services to us;
    
9. Badge Check
    
    for customers that request allocated dedicated IP addresses, for the purposes of assigning the dedicated IP address to that customer;
    
10. Badge Check
    
    personalize, assess, and improve our services, content and materials and for audience measurement purposes;
    
11. Badge Check
    
    to comply with applicable laws to which we are subject.

We may use your non-personal data to enhance the services, for instance through web analytics or troubleshooting. We may also use aggregated or depersonalized information to promote our services, such as by citing usage statistics.

5\. What are our purposes and legal basis for collecting your personal data?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

We collect your personal data because we need it to perform a contract we have signed with you or because you have taken steps to enter into a contract with us (for instance, when you fill in a contact form to request information about our services or when you sign up for an account). Otherwise, we collect personal data based on your consent for that specific purpose, and in limited purposes under legitimate interests (for example, to enable us to foster and develop our relationship (with the use of a customer relationship management system), and to perform credit checks or for verification of data and payment details).

6\. With whom do we share personal data?
----------------------------------------

Except for the limited circumstances we describe here or in an applicable agreement or our Terms of service, we do not share your personal data with third parties. When we need to provide your personal data to third parties, we will only share it to the extent necessary to provide you with our services, and we ensure that we have in place data protection requirements with these third parties (including standard contractual clauses as well as the requisite technical and organisational measures).

We may also share your personal data as required or permitted by law and as to optimally provide our services through third party providers as described below.

_Hosting Services:_ We host the website and operate the platform using third parties, including Google Cloud Platform, AWS® and Rackspace® (for our Mailjet and Mailgun products) and MacStadium, AWS® and Rackspace®, and Cyxtera (for our Email On Acid product). Your platform will be hosted from their data centers throughout the United States or Europe, based on where you have selected to deploy our services (no transfers between these separate data center locations occur).

_Payment Providers:_ We use Stripe®, Chargify, Aria, and Authorize.net to process subscription payments, and therefore provide them with the personal data required to charge your credit card and maintain any payment mandate information as law requires.

_Website functionalities and optimization:_ We may use third-party services either embedded into our website (such as Drift, Optimizely, VWO, Segment™, Split.io and Google® Analytics) or outside of it (such as GitHub®, Unbounce and Twitter®) to communicate with you or to enhance the function of the website and the services, and for product development and optimization.

_Customer engagement:_ We use third-party service providers and platforms (such as Gainsight, Customer.io, Looker, Snowflake, Salesforce, Uservoice, Zapier, and Zendesk) for customer engagement, customer chat, product feedback and customer support ticketing.

_IP addresses:_ We may share your contact information with ARIN (American Registry for Internet Numbers) for the purposes of fulfilling your request to re-assign the dedicated IP addresses.

While we provide these third parties with no more information than what is necessary to enable them to provide the services to us, any information that you provide these services providers independently is subject to their respective privacy policies and practices.

In no case do we sell, share or rent out your contacts to third parties, nor use them for any purpose other than those set forth in this policy.

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities or regulatory bodies, including to meet law enforcement requirements, in the case of a court order, a summons to appear in court or any other similar requisition from a government or the judiciary, or to establish or defend a legal application.

Additionally, we will provide information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

7\. For how long do we retain your personal data?
-------------------------------------------------

We keep your personal data for as long as is necessary to provide our services to you (unless otherwise required by law).

If you would like us to cease all of the described uses of your personal data, you may delete your account at any time from the Account Settings section of our Dashboard. This will delete your personal data from our records (within a maximum of ninety (90) days), and we will make no further use of it. We may, however, retain copies of your personal data in backups for legal retention purposes and/or for our own legitimate business purposes.

8\. How do we transfer your data?
---------------------------------

Sinch Email complies with the European General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR) as well as all applicable data protection laws. For all transfers of personal data from the EU and EEA, we maintain EU Standard contractual clauses where necessary, ensure additional safeguards such as data encryption and data minimization, as well as perform transfer impact assessments, audits and controls on our important sub processors.

You can sign our Data Processing Agreement which lists out all our important sub processors used and the measures in place to ensure proper data protections by following the link [here](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/dpa/).

9\. What are your rights in connection with personal data?
----------------------------------------------------------

In accordance with Data Protection laws, you have the right to:

1. Badge Check
    
    Request access to your personal data. This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
    
2. Badge Check
    
    Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
    
3. Badge Check
    
    Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no legitimate reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
    
4. Badge Check
    
    Withdraw your consent and opt-out from our communications. We will honor your opt-out within 14 days. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from service-related messages if you remain a customer.
    
5. Badge Check
    
    Object to processing of your personal data, for example, if we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this basis.
    
6. Badge Check
    
    Request the restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal data about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
    
7. Badge Check
    
    Request the transfer of your personal data (right to data portability).

If you want to exercise any of the above rights, please email our privacy team at [privacy@mailgun.com](mailto:privacy@mailgun.com). Sinch Email commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints should first contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@mailgun.com](mailto:privacy@mailgun.com).

Sinch Email has also committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities with regard to unresolved complaints concerning personal data transferred from the EU.

If you are located in the EU, you also have the right to lodge a complaint to your data protection authority.

10\. Security
-------------

The security and integrity of your personal information is very important to us. We follow industry accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We ensure the appropriate electronic, physical and managerial procedures are in place with a view to safeguarding and preserving all the data handled. Our infrastructure is located in top-tier data centers. Each of these locations adhere to strict physical and procedural controls which are frequently audited. Our applications are routinely scanned for vulnerabilities and an independent penetration test is conducted annually. Our employees undergo background checks (when allowed) and sign non-disclosure agreements at the time of hire.

Remember, though, that some parts of the services are public and that email, by its nature, is not a reliably private means of communication. If you voluntarily provide personal data in a public area of the website, unrelated parties online will be able to view it and collect it. If you don’t want to make this information publicly available, you shouldn’t post it.

11\. Changes
------------

The information provided in this policy may be modified to address new issues or changes. If we make significant changes, we may notify you by other means (for instance, by email or with a banner on the website) prior to the change becoming effective. Any changes we make will take effect 30 days after the update date noted [above](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/privacy-policy/). If you object to the changes, you may choose to close out your account with us before the new effective date to delete your account and related information from our records.

Last revised and updated 01/16/2023. To review a changelog and see the previous version, [click here](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/privacy-policy-old/).

* * *

**Effective January 15, 2025.**

Your privacy and security is of the utmost importance to us. We describe in this policy how we collect and use information about you in your use of our services, including our platform and the website. If you are one of our customers, you should read this policy in conjunction with our [Terms of Service](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/terms/).

1\. Who are we?
---------------

We are Sinch Email, a Sinch Group company, comprising of the brands Mailgun, Mailgun Optimize, Mailjet, and Email on Acid. The processing explained in this policy may be carried out by Sinch Email or other data controllers in the Sinch Group.

When collecting information about our customers or visitors of our website, we are, under European Union (“EU") data protection laws, qualified as “data controller". This means that we are responsible for deciding how we hold and use personal data about you.

2\. How do we collect your data?
--------------------------------

We collect information about you when you fill in a sign up or contact form on our website or send us an email. We may also receive your personal data from third parties, when you express your interest for our services to them.

We collect information by automated means. When you visit our website, view one of our advertisements on a third party-owned website, or read our marketing newsletters, we automatically collect information about you via cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies. These are small files associated with information that your browser or our servers will save and return as part of your use of the website and the services for purposes such as saving your login session between visits, remembering your display preferences, tracking your use of the website, and for audience measurement purposes. For more information on our use of cookies, read [our cookies notice](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/cookie-policy/).

3\. What data do we collect?
----------------------------

We collect two types of information about you: personal data and non-personal data.

Personal data. This is information that lets us know who you are. This includes the information you provide us when registering to use the platform (i.e. your name, company name, email address, postal address, other contact information you share with us, associated domain name and credit card information). Your login credentials are also personal data. This category also includes information tied to your identity that you provide us through other means, such as emails to our support team.

In addition, and in the context of using our services, namely creating and sending emails, we have access to the information contained in the subject and content of the emails that you send out, as well as the email contacts you send to via our services.

The data you submit should not include any sensitive personal data, such as Government identifiers (i.e. social security, driving licence, or taxpayer identification numbers), complete credit card or complete personal bank card numbers, medical records or particulars connected with applications for care or treatment associated with private individuals.

Non-personal data. This is information that doesn’t let us determine your identity. This generally comes from your use of the services after registering on our website. Non-personal data includes information that could personally identify you in its original form, but that we have modified (for instance, by aggregation) any personal data.

4\. How do we use your data?
----------------------------

If you are a visitor of our website, we use your personal and non-personal data to engage with you and support live chat conversations on the website.

When you are one of our customers, we use the information we collect about you to provide the services to you. As part of that purpose, we use your data:

1. Badge Check
    
    to create and maintain your platform account (and subaccounts), and to control access to it;
    
2. Badge Check
    
    to provide our services and facilitate performance, including verifications relating to you and for email verifications;
    
3. Badge Check
    
    to provide you with real-time logs of your use of the platform;
    
4. Badge Check
    
    to respond to any requests you may submit for support or sales information, or similar communications;
    
5. Badge Check
    
    to communicate with you about our services (for example through newsletters, marketing emails, announcements or special offers);
    
6. Badge Check
    
    for billing and collection purposes, if you have subscribed to one of our paid plans;
    
7. Badge Check
    
    for the investigation, prevention and management of fraud and for breaches of our Terms of service;
    
8. Badge Check
    
    to enable third parties to provide services to us;
    
9. Badge Check
    
    for customers that request allocated dedicated IP addresses, for the purposes of assigning the dedicated IP address to that customer;
    
10. Badge Check
    
    personalize, assess, and improve our services, content and materials and for audience measurement purposes;
    
11. Badge Check
    
    to comply with applicable laws to which we are subject.

We may use your non-personal data to enhance the services, for instance through web analytics or troubleshooting. We may also use aggregated or depersonalized information to promote our services, such as by citing usage statistics.

5\. What are our purposes and legal basis for collecting your personal data?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

We collect your personal data because we need it to perform a contract we have signed with you or because you have taken steps to enter into a contract with us (for instance, when you fill in a contact form to request information about our services or when you sign up for an account). Otherwise, we collect personal data based on your consent for that specific purpose, and in limited purposes under legitimate interests (for example, to enable us to foster and develop our relationship (with the use of a customer relationship management system), and to perform credit checks or for verification of data and payment details).

6\. With whom do we share personal data?
----------------------------------------

Except for the limited circumstances we describe here or in an applicable agreement or our Terms of service, we do not share your personal data with third parties. When we need to provide your personal data to third parties, we will only share it to the extent necessary to provide you with our services, and we ensure that we have in place data protection requirements with these third parties (including standard contractual clauses as well as the requisite technical and organisational measures).

We may also share your personal data as required or permitted by law and as to optimally provide our services through third party providers as described below.

_Hosting Services:_ We host the website and operate the platform using third parties, including Google Cloud Platform, AWS®, MacStadium and Rackspace®. Your platform will be hosted from their data centers throughout the United States or Europe, based on where you have selected to deploy our services (no transfers between these separate data center locations occur).

_Payment Providers:_ We use Stripe®, Chargify, Aria, and Authorize.net to process subscription payments, and therefore provide them with the personal data required to charge your credit card and maintain any payment mandate information as law requires.

_Website functionalities and optimization:_ We may use third-party services either embedded into our website (such as Drift, Optimizely, VWO, Segment™, Split.io and Google® Analytics) or outside of it (such as GitHub®, Unbounce and Twitter®) to communicate with you or to enhance the function of the website and the services, and for product development and optimization.

_Customer engagement:_ We use third-party service providers and platforms (such as Gainsight, Customer.io, Looker, Snowflake, Salesforce, Uservoice, Zapier, and Zendesk) for customer engagement, customer chat, product feedback and customer support ticketing.

_IP addresses:_ We may share your contact information with ARIN (American Registry for Internet Numbers) for the purposes of fulfilling your request to re-assign the dedicated IP addresses.

While we provide these third parties with no more information than what is necessary to enable them to provide the services to us, any information that you provide these services providers independently is subject to their respective privacy policies and practices.

In no case do we sell, share or rent out your contacts to third parties, nor use them for any purpose other than those set forth in this policy.

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities or regulatory bodies, including to meet law enforcement requirements, in the case of a court order, a summons to appear in court or any other similar requisition from a government or the judiciary, or to establish or defend a legal application.

Our US company, Mailgun Technologies, Inc. is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

Additionally, we will provide information to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

7\. For how long do we retain your personal data?
-------------------------------------------------

We keep your personal data for as long as is necessary to provide our services to you (unless otherwise required by law).

If you would like us to cease all of the described uses of your personal data, you may delete your account at any time from the Account Settings section of our Dashboard. This will delete your personal data from our records (within a maximum of ninety (90) days), and we will make no further use of it. We may, however, retain copies of your personal data in backups for legal retention purposes and/or for our own legitimate business purposes.

8\. How do we transfer your data?
---------------------------------

Sinch Email complies with the European General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR) as well as all applicable data protection laws. For all transfers of personal data from the EU and EEA, we maintain EU Standard contractual clauses where necessary, ensure additional safeguards such as data encryption and data minimization, as well as perform transfer impact assessments, audits and controls on our important sub processors.

Sinch Email complies with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (EU-US DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. More specifically Mailgun Technologies, Inc., our group US company, has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of Personal Data received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) Program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). Sinch Email remains responsible for all the personal information we receive under the EU-US DPF and that we subsequently transfer to third parties acting as agents on our behalf if they process personal information in a manner inconsistent with the DPF principles, unless we prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

9\. What are your rights in connection with personal data?
----------------------------------------------------------

In accordance with Data Protection laws, you have the right to:

1. Badge Check
    
    Request access to your personal data. This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
    
2. Badge Check
    
    Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
    
3. Badge Check
    
    Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no legitimate reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
    
4. Badge Check
    
    Withdraw your consent and opt-out from our communications. We will honor your opt-out within 14 days. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from service-related messages if you remain a customer.
    
5. Badge Check
    
    Object to processing of your personal data, for example, if we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this basis.
    
6. Badge Check
    
    Request the restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal data about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
    
7. Badge Check
    
    Request the transfer of your personal data (right to data portability).

If you want to exercise any of the above rights, please email our privacy team at [privacy@mailgun.com](mailto:privacy@mailgun.com). Sinch Email commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints should first contact our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@sinch.com](https://www.mailgun.com/privacy-policy/dpo@sinch.com).

Sinch Email has also committed to cooperate and comply, in compliance with the EU-US DPF and the UK Extension to the EU\_US DPF, with the advice of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPA) and the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) with regard to unresolved complaints concerning personal data received in reliance on the EU-US DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-US DPF.

You have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration as per the EU-US DPF Principles Annex. If you are located in the EU, you also have the right to lodge a complaint to your DPA.

You can sign our Data Processing Agreement which lists out all our important sub-processors used and the measures in place to ensure proper data protections.

10\. Security
-------------

The security and integrity of your personal information is very important to us. We follow industry accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. We ensure the appropriate electronic, physical and managerial procedures are in place with a view to safeguarding and preserving all the data handled. Our infrastructure is located in top-tier data centers. Each of these locations adhere to strict physical and procedural controls which are frequently audited. Our applications are routinely scanned for vulnerabilities and an independent penetration test is conducted annually. Our employees undergo background checks (when allowed) and sign non-disclosure agreements at the time of hire.

Remember, though, that some parts of the services are public and that email, by its nature, is not a reliably private means of communication. If you voluntarily provide personal data in a public area of the website, unrelated parties online will be able to view it and collect it. If you don’t want to make this information publicly available, you shouldn’t post it.

11\. Changes
------------

The information provided in this policy may be modified to address new issues or changes. If we make significant changes, we may notify you by other means (for instance, by email or with a banner on the website) prior to the change becoming effective. Any changes we make will take effect 30 days after the update date noted [above](https://www.mailgun.com/legal/privacy-policy/). If you object to the changes, you may choose to close out your account with us before the new effective date to delete your account and related information from our records.

Last revised 01/15/2025.

* deliv-team@mailgun.company
* outbound-sales@mailgun.company
* spamtrapmonitoring@mailgun.company
* iceman@mailgun.top
* admiral@mailgun.top
* timduncan@mailgun.top

Follow us

Products

Solutions

Enterprise

Resources

Help

Company

### Products

### Solutions

### Enterprise

### Resources

### Help

### Company

Copyright ©2024 Mailgun. All Rights Reserved.
